# Gurbakshish Singh

(M.NO-8968598989,hny089@gmail.com)

G.K. Vihar, Manakwal Road, Dugri, Ludhiana, Punjab.

# **OBJECTIVE**

Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with a wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Handles any part of the process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 3 years of related experience.

#### **EDUCATION**

MSC.IT	2021
Lovely Professional University(Distance Education)	
PGDCA	2020
Lovely Professional University(Distance Education)	
Bachelor Of Business Administration	2045
Lovely Professional University(Distance Education)	2017
10+2, Commerce	2013
Atam Public Sr. Sec. School, Ludhiana	
10th	2011
Atam Public Se. Sec. School, Ludhiana	

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### **Evolvan Solutions Info (PVT Ltd)**

July 2021 - Present

Full Stack Developer

- Reviewed code, debugged problems and corrected issues.
- Developed functional databases, applications and servers to support websites on the backend.
- Analyzed existing software implementations to identify areas requiring improvement.
- Used ReactJS, NodeJS, PHP, DRUPAL and MYSQL/POSTGRESQL/FIREBASE to develop and manage databases.
- Client Handling and work according to their requirements.

- Worked with back-end developers to design APIs.
- Coordinated efficient large-scale software deployments.
- Contributed ideas and suggestions in team meetings and delivered updates on deadlines, designs and enhancements.
- Solved Hacking Issues and secured the sites from hacking like cross site scripting, file inclusion vulnerability etc.

# LN WEB WORKS (PVT Ltd)

December 2019 - July 2021

Web Developer

- Worked On API's.
- Worked on Many Servers like siteground, AWS, Pantheon, Acquia Cloud etc.
- Created Custom Modules and themes.
- Migrated Drupal sites From D7 to D8
- Worked On Technologies Drupal, PHP, jquery.

#### **Etude PRO**

April 2019 - November 2019

Web Developer

- Worked On Module Like CRM similar to Salesforce
- Payment Gateway Integration with many websites
- Worked on technologies like php, cpanel.
- Worked on technologies like php, javascript, ajax, mysql.

## **TECHNICAL STRENGTHS**

- 1. Front End: HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript/jQuery.
- 2. Servers: Apache Server Side.
- 3. Scripting: PHP, React JS, Node JS
- 4. Database: MySQLi Programming.
- 5. Client Side Scripting: JavaScript, Jquery Ajax.
- 6. Git.

#### **KEY PROJECTS**

Many other online websites and related modules

https://winemaps.com/

https://secan.com/

# https://celebvm.com/

https://coolmathgames.com

https://tenant.dev.teamzskill.com

Payment Gateway Integration like payubiz, paypal, stripes etc.

# PERSONAL PROFILE

**Date Of Birth** 12 September, 1995

**Permanent address** G.K. Vihar, Manakwal Road, Ludhiana,

Punjab.

**Contact No** 8968598989